Upvotes: 942
URL: https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/1gi1zbg/tifu_by_squeezing_my_hands_together/
Content:
This happened yesterday, but I needed a day to recover.
I’m a tech executive at a midsize company
I have a new team member—a younger female who is sharp, talented and professional
She just started, so we haven’t gotten to know each other very well
She was in my office for a meeting
I was at my desk wrapping something up, and she was sitting at the small meeting desk in my office, working on something while she waited
She wasn’t looking at me.
I finished and sent an email, then turned to join her at the desk
As I did, I pressed my hands together as if to indicate “ok, on to the next thing.”
Out of my hands comes the beefiest fart noise you can imagine
It literally startled me
She didn’t flinch, but there was definitely a shift in the room.
I didn’t know what to do
I wasn’t 100% sure she heard it, so it seemed weird to bring it up
I even tried squeezing my hands together a couple more times to make it happen again, but no such luck
Now I might always be the boss who blasted ass all over the office.
tl;dr: My hands farted and ruined my professional credibility