Upvotes: 1405
URL: https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/1gjjce7/tifu_by_not_thinking_when_i_threw_stuff_out/
Content:
A small one, but I found it funny
My dog and constant companion for the last 14 years passed away recently
I decided to clean up and threw out a bunch of her stuff
Including her dog bed and way too many toys
Including several very loud squeaky toys.
The trash pickup is bright and early this morning
Happened to be while I was looking out the window and making my morning coffee
The sanitation worker dumped the bags into the truck then immediately hit the lever to compact the garbage
As I mentioned it was early morning, and there were several startlingly loud toys, which scream out when squeezed
Yes the worker definitely heard the noise, and stopped the compactor from any further movement
I'm glad to report that emergency services were not notified about living things being thrown away and crushed.
TL;DR as required
TIFU by throwing a bunch of squeaky toys in the garbage.