Upvotes: 19
URL: https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/1gmddrl/tifu_by_verbally_expressing_my_discomfort/
Content:
Okay first thing to know about me is that I am socially a dumbass
I cannot for the life of me function in social interactions
I’m terrible at talking to people and idk, I always just seem to drown with anything social.
I also would like to make it known that for whatever reason, lately I have been extremely motion sensitive
Meaning that out of the blue riding in the back seat of a car feels like being on a roller coaster for me
Okay, so today I hire an Uber to run me up to the post office
Simple
For any one but me :(
Right off the bat the car starts moving and I feel that horrible feeling of my stomach dropping
I panic, I don’t know what to do and unconsciously I end up making whimpers of pain noises
And as I do this I’m pretty sure my driver thinks I’m insane because when she slows down or stop I’m completely fine and stop doing it
And then what do I do? Instead of doing the sensible thing and explaining that I am car sick, can you please slow down no! Forget reason and logic
How stupid that I would even dare to think that! No, what I do instead is apologize and then say I’m getting over a cold
Am embarrassed? Yes
Am I feeling stupid? 100%
I think above all though I just feel sad that something as simple as my errand can wind up being a complete disaster when it should just be so easy.
TL;DR: I can’t handle motion anymore and when I tried to go to the post office I ended up making whimpering pain noises.