Upvotes: 24
URL: https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/1gm27sg/tifu_by_bricking_my_phone_completely_avoidable/
Content:
If you've ever used a phone by a Chinese company, you'll note they have a tendency to run like crap, filter your photos, and sell your data (so does Google) so naturally, I wanted to install a custom rom
Sure, that's the first solution you think of
It went so well
Bootloader unlocked all at my own risk, and then I try to flash the rom
Not enough space, after some research I found I could delete the "product" partition at my own risk
Having not specified a or b, I thought nothing of it
Half way through going to boot TWRP, it decides to reboot
Having deleted userdata, adb debugging came pre-disabled
It now continuously vibrates and reboots shaming me for killing it
Its only input to the outside world is displaying "Redmi" over and over, and I have no way into it.
£200 mistake
Not my worst work.
TL;DR buy a Google Pixel
Edit: no need to downvote everything, I know I'm an idiot that's why anyone posts here.
Edit again: Fastboot nope
Recovery nope.
Also edit: Get it in your head, I cannot splurge on a phone all at once
It has to be pay monthly or nothing
Ergo debating dumbphone
Edit: Redmi Note 10 5G
Edit: MTK Client is the solution to all my problems
Today I Un-f\*\*\*ed Up.