Upvotes: 388
URL: https://www.reddit.com/r/tifu/comments/1gikorf/tifu_by_realising_why_the_funds_in_my_account_was/
Content:
Working cross border and getting my salary in another country and currency than were I Iive, I’ve always tried very hard to have an account intended for my bills
It should always contain about the same amount going out every month
Thus ensuring I can pay them even if my salary has not yet been transferred over
Well
This summer I also got two very cute cats
And I’ve been buying (probably too many) things for them
So my bills account has been lower than normal, as I’ve not been paying everything directly with my card
Today I checked my account to make sure everything is payed and that the balance is where it should be
Couldn’t figure why it was so low
As the accounts is for almost only bills, I can get a monthly overview pretty fast when I look it over
I notice this one monthly expense being double booked
On nooo, I must have processed it twice
One of the larger ones too covering both parking and the fee to the owners association in my building
Make a search
Notice I did the same thing last month
Time to call them I guess
And figure out if they’ll repay me, or if I just don’t have to pay for parking and the fee to the owners association in the building I live in
Almost $500 a month
🤦🏼‍♀️
TL;DR : messed up paying my bills, and overpayed by almost $1.000 over 2 months
I just thought I’d bought waaaay too many things for my new cats
Because they’re worth it
😻